const questions = {
  easy: [
    {
      question: "What is the value of x in the equation 5x = 25?",
      answer: "5",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 3x + 4 = 19",
      answer: "5",
    },
    {
      question: "Find the value of x if 2x + 6 = 10",
      answer: "2",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 4x - 3 = 9",
      answer: "3",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the value of x in the equation 6x + 7 = 25?",
      answer: "3",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 2x + 5 = 13",
      answer: "4",
    },
    {
      question: "Find the value of x if 5x - 10 = 15",
      answer: "5",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 6x + 3 = 33",
      answer: "5",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the value of x in the equation 4x - 2 = 10?",
      answer: "3",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 7x - 4 = 45",
      answer: "7",
    },
  ],
  medium: [
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 2(x + 4) = 24",
      answer: "8",
    },
    {
      question: "Find the value of x if 3x - 7 = 8x - 22",
      answer: "3",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 5(2x - 1) = 15",
      answer: "2",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the value of x in the equation 3x - 5 = 7x - 19?",
      answer: "3",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 2x + 7 = 3x - 4",
      answer: "-11",
    },
    {
      question: "Find the value of x if 4(x + 5) = 56",
      answer: "6",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 3(x - 2) = 27",
      answer: "11",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the value of x in the equation 2(x + 3) - 3(x - 1) = 1?",
      answer: "1/5",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 2(3x - 1) = 4x + 7",
      answer: "5",
    },
    {
      question: "Find the value of x if 2x - 5 = 11 - 3x",
      answer: "2",
    },
  ],
  hard: [
    {
      question: "What is the value of x in the equation 2x - 3 = 7x + 8?",
      answer: "-2.2",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 3x + 4 = 2x - 5",
      answer: "-9",
    },
    {
      question: "Find the value of x if 2(3x - 4) = 14x + 6",
      answer: "2",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 2x + 3(x - 4) = 9",
      answer: "5",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the value of x in the equation 5(2x - 1) - 2(3x + 1) = -8?",
      answer: "3/7",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the value of x in the equation 4x + 3 = 3x + 7?",
      answer: "4",
    },
    {
      question: "Find the value of x if (x + 3)/5 - 2 = (3x - 1)/2",
      answer: "11",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 2x - 1 = x^2 - 6x + 5",
      answer: "3",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the value of x in the equation (x + 2)/(2x - 1) = (x - 1)/(x + 3)?",
      answer: "-1",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 4x + 7 = 2(x^2 - 3)",
      answer: "2, -1/2",
    },
    {
      question: "Find the value of x if (x - 3)/4 - (x + 2)/2 = 1",
      answer: "9",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: 3(x - 1) - 4(x + 2) = 5 - 2x",
      answer: "-2",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the value of x in the equation 2x - 1 = sqrt(3x + 4)?",
      answer: "3",
    },
    {
      question: "Solve for x: (x - 2)/(x + 3) + (x + 1)/(x - 4) = 2",
      answer: "-5/3",
    },
    {
      question: "Find the value of x if 4/x + 1 = 2/(x - 2)",
      answer: "4",
    },
  ],
};

module.exports = questions;
